<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jorrod.com on Jorrod</title>
    <link>https://jorrod.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jorrod.com on Jorrod</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jorrod.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Check Your Daily Calories Burned with an Apple Watch</title>
      <link>https://jorrod.com/check-daily-calories-burned-apple-watch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorrod.com/check-daily-calories-burned-apple-watch/</guid>
      <description>Ever wondered exactly how many calories you burn in a day? Well, you&amp;rsquo;re in for a treat because we&amp;rsquo;re about to unravel the magic of calorie tracking with your trusty sidekick – the Apple Watch. It&amp;rsquo;s not just a sleek accessory; it&amp;rsquo;s your fitness confidant. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;re going to dive into the nitty-gritty of how to check the total number of calories you burn every day using this amazing gadget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Adjust Your Fiskars Reel Mower</title>
      <link>https://jorrod.com/adjusting-reel-mower/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorrod.com/adjusting-reel-mower/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of uneven, patchy grass on your lawn? It&amp;rsquo;s time to take charge of your lawn care game. One essential step to achieving a beautifully manicured lawn is properly adjusting your mower. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry; it&amp;rsquo;s easier than you think and we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the process below.
Why Adjust Your Fiskars Reel Mower? Before we jump into the &amp;ldquo;how&amp;rdquo;, let&amp;rsquo;s understand the &amp;ldquo;why&amp;rdquo;. Adjusting your mower is essential for a couple of reasons:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Chess Tactics: The Art of Forking</title>
      <link>https://jorrod.com/chess-fork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorrod.com/chess-fork/</guid>
      <description>Today, we&amp;rsquo;re diving into one of the coolest moves in the chess playbook: forking. Now, you might think we&amp;rsquo;re talking about dinner table etiquette, but in the chess world, forking is a sneaky tactic that can turn the game in your favor. So, grab your favorite chessboard, and let&amp;rsquo;s unravel the mysteries of forking!
Imagine this: you move your knight in a way that attacks two of your opponent&amp;rsquo;s pieces at once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chess 101: How Every Piece Moves</title>
      <link>https://jorrod.com/how-each-chess-piece-moves/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorrod.com/how-each-chess-piece-moves/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Chess is one of those classic games that can seem intimidating at first, but it&amp;rsquo;s all about taking one step at a time. To get started, you&amp;rsquo;ll want to understand how each piece on the board moves. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll break down the basics for you, making it easy for you to get the hang of the king, queen, rook, bishop, knight, and pawn.
The King First up, we&amp;rsquo;ve got the king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chess 101: How to Set Up a Chess Board</title>
      <link>https://jorrod.com/how-to-set-up-a-chess-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorrod.com/how-to-set-up-a-chess-board/</guid>
      <description>So, you&amp;rsquo;ve decided to embark on a journey into the captivating world of chess. Kudos to you! Before you get your game face on and start planning your grandmaster strategy, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to master the basics. And that begins with setting up your chess board correctly. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry; it&amp;rsquo;s not as daunting as it might seem. Let&amp;rsquo;s break it down, step by step.
The Basics: What You Need First things first, make sure you&amp;rsquo;ve got all your gear ready.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chess Basics: Learn How to Play Chess</title>
      <link>https://jorrod.com/learn-how-to-play-chess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorrod.com/learn-how-to-play-chess/</guid>
      <description>Chessboard and Setup Chessboard: Chess is played on a square board with 64 squares arranged in an 8x8 grid. The board should be placed so that each player has a white square on their right-hand side.
Chess Pieces: There are 32 pieces in chess, divided equally between two players. Each player has:
 1 King 1 Queen 2 Rooks 2 Knights 2 Bishops 8 Pawns  Setup: Place the pieces on the board as shown below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jorrod.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorrod.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey. I’m a father, husband, and IT professional. When I have free time, I love nerding out and learning all I can about random topics. I’ll be sharing the tips and tricks I pick up along the way so that you can save time researching them and get right to business.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
